(Sheldon:)how much lunch money
has been taken from us?
(Sheldon:)How many kites?
(Sheldon:)How many Scooby-Doo
Trapper Keepers?
(Raj:)I totally had one of those.
(Sheldon:)Of course you did.
(Sheldon:)It was a fun and practical way
of organizing your school work.
(Sheldon:)But the bullies
took it from us.
(Sheldon:)Well, no more.
(Sheldon:)Tonight, we take back
our dignity,
(Sheldon:)our birthright and our pride.
(Sheldon:)What do you say?
(Sheldon:)Who's with me?
(Raj:)I have a hip-hop aerobics class
at 5:00; could we go after?
(Amy:)Sure.
(Howard:)Also, tonight's the Sabbath
(Howard:)and my mother and I
have a tradition of
lighting the candles and
watching Wheel of Fortune, so...
If we could leave
at 8:00, we'd still be able to
regain our birthright
at 10:00, 10:30 latest.
(Policeman:)Fine.
(Sheldon:)Leonard?
Oh, geez, I-I don't know
if I can ditch Priya
(Leonard:)two nights in a row.
(Raj:)Oh, come on, man.
(Raj:)Bros before...
(Raj:)...my sister.